http://www.jcvi.org/internet-usage-privacy-statement

Internet Usage & Privacy Statement
The J. Craig Venter Institute (JCVI) has several domain names which can be used to access JCVI web sites (Site or Sites). Such domain names include jcvi.org, tigr.org and other JCVI domain names. These Sites are controlled, operated and maintained by JCVI personnel in connection with JCVI business. Please read this statement carefully before accessing any Sites or conducting any transaction available at Sites. By using any of the Sites the user signifies that they have read this statement and agree to be bound by and comply with it. JCVI reserves the right to modify these terms at any time and will publish notice of any such modifications at this Site or elsewhere.
1. Collection of Personal Information
JCVI does not automatically collect any personal information about user when user visits Sites. Personal information is only collected from user if user provided that information voluntarily. Examples of voluntarily provided information include sending JCVI an e-mail or completing an online form. JCVI will use the information provided by user to respond to user's message or inquiry. E-mails are treated in the same manner as letters sent to JCVI, therefore, information will not be collected for commercial marketing.
2. Information Automatically Collected
Although JCVI does not collect any personal information, there is some information that is automatically collected. The information that is automatically collected includes:
1. The Internet Protocol (IP) address or host name of the computer that accessed the website. An IP address only identifies the computer and not the user.
2. The type of browser, its version and the operating system used to access the Sites.
3. The date and time user accessed the Sites.
4. The pages user visits.
5. The content length of any document sent to user.
6. The request method used.
7. The Universal Resource Identifier (URI) and any associated query string which defines the location of a resource on the server.
8. The transport protocol and the version used.
9. If user linked to the Sites from another website, the address of that website.
The information above is automatically collected to help make Sites more useful to its users. JCVI usually does not create a record or track information about individual users and their visits. However, JCVI reserves the right to track users if JCVI reasonably believes that the Sites are being wrongfully accessed and/or abused.
3. Cookies
JCVI may use cookies. A cookie is a small file containing information that is sent to a user's Web browser to distinguish users of web sites. The use of cookies is a regular practice among Internet web sites. Sites may occasionally use both persistent and non-persistent cookies to enhance or improve user's visit to Sites. Non-persistent cookies are created automatically on the instrument user is employing to access Sites. A non-persistent cookie is erased when user's Web browser is closed. Persistent cookies are stored on user's hard drive. These types of cookies allow Sites to recognize user upon subsequent visits which may facilitate user's preference for certain features available on Sites. User should note that the majority of Web browsers accept cookies, however there may be options available on user's browser that may prevent the accepting or receiving of cookies. If cookies are not accepted, there is a possibility that the complete functionality of Sites may be impaired.
4. Security of Information
JCVI employs reasonable measures to protect information from unauthorized access or disclosure. If user communication includes personal information that they do not wish to provide electronically, please contact JCVI by postal mail or telephone.
5. Links to Other Sites
Sites may include hyperlinks to web sites maintained or controlled by others. JCVI is not responsible for and does not routinely review, approve or endorse the contents of or use of any of the products or services that may be offered at these web sites.
6. Use Limitations
User may use Sites for legal purposes only. User may not use JCVI computing resources or Sites to disseminate unsolicited advertising or promotional material of any kind. JCVI has the right to remove material from Sites or take other action at its sole discretion. Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on Sites are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution under Title 18 U.S.C., §1001, §1030 and applicable Maryland law.
7. Disclaimer of Warranty
JCVI SITES AND ANY INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES THEREIN ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR USE OF A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT.
JCVI does not warrant that sites will operate in an uninterrupted or error-free manner or that the Sites are free of viruses or other harmful components. Use of information from or through these Sites is at user's own risk.
8. Limitation of Liability
USER AGREES THAT JCVI WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGES, EITHER ACTUAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS, OR TO USER'S OR ANY THIRD PARTIES USE OR INABILITY TO USE A SITE, OR TO USER'S RELIANCE UPON INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM OR THROUGH A SITE. IN PARTICULAR, JCVI WILL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, WHETHER FORSEEABLE OR UNFORSEEABLE (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, CLAIMS FOR DEFAMATION, ERRORS, LOSS OF DATA, OR INTERRUPTION IN AVAILABILITY OF DATA), ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS, USER'S USE OR INABILITY TO USE A SITE, OR ANY PURCHASES ON THIS SITE, OR TO USER'S RELIANCE UPON INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM OR THROUGH A SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, STATUTORY, OR OTHER LAW, EXCEPT ONLY IN THE CASE OF DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY WHERE AND ONLY TO THE EXTENT THAT APPLICABLE LAW REQUIRES SUCH LIABILITY.
JCVI makes no representation regarding user's ability to transmit and receive information from or through the Sites and user agrees and acknowledges that user's ability to access the Sites may be impaired. JCVI disclaims any and all liability resulting from or related to such events.
9. Trademarks
The logo, name and all graphics on Sites are trademarks of JCVI. Use, reproduction, copying or redistribution of trademarks, without the written permission of JCVI is prohibited. All other logos, names and graphics appearing on Sites are the marks of their respective owners. Please contact the respective owners for use of their trademarks.
10. Copyright
The content on the Sites is copyrighted. User may not reproduce, republish, or incorporate text or images from the Sites into other media including, but not limited to, web sites, publications and any materials user or others produce without the express permission of the copyright holder. Permission must be granted by JCVI or when applicable, by the original copyright holder, if user intends to use content from the Sites for such purposes. For all other purposes JCVI asks that user credit the original source by including the appropriate copyright notation. It is the user's responsibility to be aware of current copyright law and its applications and to contact the copyright holder for permission to use non-JCVI copyrighted material. The user agrees to indemnify JCVI from any costs or claims for infringement of copyright in relation to copies of images or text from the Sites. JCVI respects the intellectual property rights of others. If user believes that a copyright has been violated on Sites, please notify us. This copyright notice applies only to the Sites.
11. Comments/Questions
If there are any comments or questions regarding this statement or any JCVI Sites please contact us.
In the News
JCVI President Karen Nelson, Ph.D., Recognized as Global Scientific Pioneer on Clarivate’s Highly Cited Researcher 2020 List
What's Happening
Unique Antibody Pattern Discovered in COVID-19 ICU Patients May Be Key to Predicting Severe Outcomes
Recently Published
Publisher Correction: A community-based transcriptomics classification and nomenclature of neocortical cell types.
